[A Mission of the Heart]
[مهمة القلب]
[Episode 10]
[الحلقة 10]
Qiulan.
تشيولان.
Think hard. You've seen it before.
فكّر جيدًا، لقد رأيت ذلك من قبل.
I'm trying.
انا احاول.
Just a moment, please.
لحظة من فضلك.
It's coming back to me now.
لقد عاد إلي الآن.
I saw it in Ms. Liu's jewelry box.
رأيته في صندوق مجوهرات السيدة ليو.
At that time,
في ذلك الوقت،
she was muttering about it.
كانت تتمتم بهذا الشأن.
Just a worthless stone like this
مجرد حجر لا قيمة له مثل هذا
deserves to be kept carefully?
هل يستحق أن يتم الاحتفاظ به بعناية؟
It clearly isn't anything valuable.
من الواضح أنه ليس شيئًا ذا قيمة.
What was Lord Chen thinking?
ماذا كان يفكر اللورد تشين؟
This Lord Chen
هذا اللورد تشين
is Chen Zhao?
هو تشين تشاو؟
Yes.
نعم.
Could this be the thing the mysterious man in black
هل يمكن أن يكون هذا هو الشيء الذي فعله الرجل الغامض باللون الأسود؟
was looking for last night?
كنت أبحث عن الليلة الماضية؟
It should be.
ينبغي أن يكون.
One piece belongs to Wang Mang.
قطعة واحدة تعود إلى وانغ مانج.
The other one belongs to Chen Zhao.
والآخر ينتمي إلى تشين تشاو.
Wang Mang is the thief who stole the relief funds.
وانغ مانغ هو اللص الذي سرق أموال الإغاثة.
So this means
لذا هذا يعني
Chen Zhao was involved in the relief fund theft case.
كان تشين تشاو متورطًا في قضية سرقة صندوق الإغاثة.
It's just that we don't know
إنه فقط أننا لا نعرف
how many people are behind this.
كم عدد الأشخاص الذين يقفون وراء هذا؟
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
the person who snuck into the Chen Mansion last night
الشخص الذي تسلل إلى قصر تشين الليلة الماضية
is also involved in the relief fund theft case?
هل هو متورط أيضًا في قضية سرقة صندوق الإغاثة؟
Maybe he's the one who killed Chen Zhao.
ربما هو الذي قتل تشين تشاو.
Why didn't you catch him then?
لماذا لم تمسكه إذن؟
I...
أنا...
He couldn't use his internal energy at that time,
لم يكن يستطيع استخدام طاقته الداخلية في ذلك الوقت،
because he was affected by...
لأنه تأثر ب...
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I didn't know that person's identity at that time.
لم أكن أعرف هوية هذا الشخص في ذلك الوقت.
I was afraid of alerting the enemy.
كنت خائفة من تنبيه العدو.
I just don't know
انا فقط لا اعرف
what the stone is actually used for.
ما هو استخدام الحجر فعليا؟
Is it a symbol of membership in their organization?
هل هو رمز للعضوية في منظمتهم؟
No.
لا.
If that were the case,
لو كان الأمر كذلك،
that person last night wouldn't have needed to steal it.
لم يكن ذلك الشخص بحاجة إلى سرقته الليلة الماضية.
It looks like a key.
يبدو وكأنه مفتاح.
A key?
مفتاح؟
This could be
هذا يمكن أن يكون
a puzzle piece of a key to a treasure.
قطعة من لغز مفتاح الكنز.
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
They hid the stolen relief funds
لقد أخفوا أموال الإغاثة المسروقة
in a very secret place.
في مكان سري للغاية.
And each person
وكل شخص
has a part of the key.
لديه جزء من المفتاح.
To get the money,
للحصول على المال،
they must use all the key pieces
يجب عليهم استخدام جميع القطع الرئيسية
to open the door.
لفتح الباب.
That must be it.
يجب أن يكون هذا هو الأمر.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
you lost the only clue last night.
لقد فقدت الدليل الوحيد الليلة الماضية.
Now how are you going to track down the mastermind behind this?
الآن كيف ستتمكن من تعقب العقل المدبر وراء هذا؟
It's not impossible.
إنه ليس مستحيلا.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Everyone knows about the relationship between Chen Zhao and Liu Mei'er.
الجميع يعرف العلاقة بين تشين تشاو وليو ماير.
We only need
نحن نحتاج فقط
to subtly spread the news that this stone
لنشر الخبر بطريقة خفية بأن هذا الحجر
is in Liu Mei'er's hands.
في يد ليو ماير.
The mastermind will reveal themselves.
العقل المدبر سوف يكشف عن نفسه.
Yu, you're so smart.
يو، أنت ذكي جدًا.
But
لكن
you two are too handsome and eye-catching.
أنتما الاثنان جميلان للغاية وملفتان للأنظار.
You've also been frequenting Xiafeng House lately.
لقد كنت أيضًا تتردد على منزل Xiafeng في الآونة الأخيرة.
You definitely can't just walk in like this.
بالتأكيد لا يمكنك المشي بهذه الطريقة.
How do we get in then?
كيف ندخل إذن؟
Mr. Li, we've been waiting for you!
السيد لي، لقد كنا في انتظارك!
Drink more!
اشرب المزيد!
We're almost there, Mr. Huang.
لقد وصلنا تقريبا إلى هناك، السيد هوانغ.
The girl you asked for
الفتاة التي طلبتها
is inside.
هو في الداخل.
Don't let anyone disturb us.
لا تدع أحدا يزعجنا.
I understand.
أفهم.
Mr. Huang, enjoy yourself.
السيد هوانغ، استمتع.
I won't take up any more of your time.
لن أستغرق المزيد من وقتك.
Alright, I'll reward both of you.
حسنًا، سأكافئكما.
I'll reward both of you.
سأكافئكما.
I'll reward both of you!
سأكافئكما!
After him!
بعده!
Damn it. We lost him.
يا للعار، لقد فقدناه.
His lightness skill is incredible.
مهارته في الخفة لا تصدق.
Even with our combined effort, we couldn't catch up.
حتى مع جهودنا المشتركة، لم نتمكن من اللحاق بالركب.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Let's head back first.
دعونا نعود أولا.
I have failed in my duty
لقد فشلت في أداء واجبي
to retrieve the Moon Stone.
لاسترجاع حجر القمر.
Please punish me, Master.
من فضلك عاقبني يا سيدي.
Who has the Moon Stone now?
من لديه حجر القمر الآن؟
Lu Zhan.
لو زان.
I'm afraid Wang Mang's Moon Stone
أخشى أن يكون حجر القمر لـ وانغ مانج
is also in his hands.
وهو أيضا بين يديه.
I never expected that Lu Zhan would still
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن لو تشان سيظل
beat us to it.
لقد سبقنا إلى ذلك.
I will definitely get the Moon Stone back!
سأستعيد حجر القمر بالتأكيد!
Do not act rashly.
لا تتصرف بتهور.
Lu Zhan is highly skilled in martial arts
لو تشان يتمتع بمهارة عالية في فنون الدفاع عن النفس
and ruthless in his methods.
وقاسي في أساليبه.
If we make one wrong move,
إذا قمنا بخطوة خاطئة واحدة،
he'll likely catch us out.
من المرجح أن يمسك بنا.
We need to plan carefully.
نحن بحاجة إلى التخطيط بعناية.
You should lie low for a while.
ينبغي عليك أن تختبئ لفترة من الوقت.
Yes.
نعم.
Is it delicious, Yu?
هل هو لذيذ، يو؟
Yes, it is!
نعم إنه كذلك!
Who eats such rich food for breakfast?
من يأكل مثل هذا الطعام الغني على الإفطار؟
That's a total recipe for indigestion!
هذه وصفة كاملة لعسر الهضم!
Looks like I prepared this for nothing.
يبدو أنني قمت بإعداد هذا من أجل لا شيء.
Some people just don't appreciate it.
بعض الناس لا يقدرون ذلك.
I think I might as well throw it away.
أعتقد أنني قد أتخلص منه أيضًا.
No, My Lord!
لا يا سيدي!
It'd be such a waste
سيكون هذا مضيعة كبيرة
to throw this lavish meal away.
التخلص من هذه الوجبة الفاخرة.
I'll eat it!
سوف آكله!
What's going on with these two?
ماذا يحدث مع هذين الاثنين؟
It's just a handkerchief.
إنها مجرد منديل.
Is there really any need to fight over it?
هل هناك حقا أي حاجة للقتال عليه؟
My Lord.
سيدي.
Someone found Zhang Chuchu's body
لقد عثر أحدهم على جثة تشانغ تشوتشو
in the mass grave.
في المقبرة الجماعية.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Let's hurry over there!
دعونا نسرع ​​إلى هناك!
When was the body discovered?
متى تم اكتشاف الجثة؟
A heavy rain the day before yesterday caused a landslide.
تسببت الأمطار الغزيرة التي هطلت أمس في حدوث انهيار أرضي.
Zhang Chuchu's coffin was washed out.
تم غسل نعش تشانغ تشوتشو.
Someone found it this morning and reported it.
لقد وجده شخص ما هذا الصباح وأبلغ عنه.
How awful.
كم هو فظيع.
The deceased is Zhang Chuchu,
المتوفى هو تشانغ تشوتشو،
the top courtesan at Xiafeng House.
أفضل العاهرة في منزل شيا فنغ.
She was around 23 years old.
وكان عمرها حوالي 23 عامًا.
She has been dead for about 10 days.
لقد ماتت منذ حوالي 10 أيام.
There are
هناك
multiple whip marks and binding wounds on her body.
علامات سوط متعددة وجروح ربط على جسدها.
This suggests that before her death,
وهذا يشير إلى أنه قبل وفاتها،
she might have been imprisoned
ربما تم سجنها
and severely tortured.
وتعرض للتعذيب الشديد.